<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <title><![CDATA[Carlos Nascimento]]></title>
    <link href="https://carloscdf.github.io/carlos/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
    <link href="https://carloscdf.github.io/carlos/"/>
    <updated>2023-06-09T00:48:53+00:00</updated>
    <id>https://carloscdf.github.io/carlos/</id>
            <author>
            <name><![CDATA[Carlos Nascimento]]></name>            <email><![CDATA[henrique.duplex@hotmail.com]]></email>        </author>
        <generator uri="http://sculpin.io/">Sculpin</generator>
            <entry>
            <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Journey into the Tech World: My Introduction, Passion for Web Development, and About this Blog.]]></title>
            <link href="https://carloscdf.github.io/carlos/article/a-journey-into-the-tech-world-my-introduction-passion-for-web-development-and-about-this-blog/"/>
            <updated>2023-06-09T00:48:53+00:00</updated>
            <id>https://carloscdf.github.io/carlos/article/a-journey-into-the-tech-world-my-introduction-passion-for-web-development-and-about-this-blog/</id>
            <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Hello, world. Well, this is my first official post here. I'm just testing to check if everything is right. So let's get started.</p>

<p>First, I want to introduce myself and summarize how I entered the tech world.</p>

<h2 id="about-me-and-how-i-entered-the-tech-world.">About me and how I entered the Tech world.</h2>

<p>I'm Carlos Nascimento, and I live in Bahia, Brazil. I started in the tech world when I was very young. I learned a lot because I have always been a curious person.</p>

<p><strong>When I was 16 years old, I was accepted at IFBA (Bahia Federal Institute of Education, Science, and Technology) in Jequié City</strong>. However, I didn't study in person for a long time because the COVID-19 pandemic came, and the world stopped. It was at that time that I decided to study web development by taking the <strong>"Desenhista de Produtos Gráficos Web"</strong> course offered by IFBA during the pandemic.</p>

<p>When I completed the course, I realized how powerful and magical web development is. <strong>So, I decided to search and learn more about it</strong>. This was the first step towards everything that was going to come in the future.</p>

<p>I'm also a <strong>Graphic Designer</strong> but it's more like a hobby to me.</p>

<p>I worked on some projects during this process, as you can see on my <a href="https://github.com/carloscdf">GitHub</a>, but unfortunately, I didn't post all of them there.</p>

<p>It has been three years, and here I am. Currently, I'm totally in love with web development, I learned a lot during the pandemic such as <strong>HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and PHP.</strong> I'm excited to learn more and more, but now starting with <strong>Python</strong>. I want to dive into the river of <strong>Artificial Intelligence</strong> and do amazing projects. <strong>This is my life goal and what I'm focused on</strong>.</p>

<p>I'm 18 years old now, still studying web development at IFBA and at home as well, and I'm almost done with my secondary education with a technical specialization this year. I'm excited about what the future holds for me.</p>

<p>Okay... so let's talk about this blog.</p>

<h2 id="about-the-blog.">About the blog.</h2>

<p>I created this blog to share everything I know, a little about my life, and experiences I've been through, and the ones that are yet to come. Here, I will post tutorials about a lot of things. The focus is on programming, but not on a specific language because <strong>I want to talk about all of them</strong>. We will also work on some projects. I want this blog to be a fountain of knowledge and helpful to all of you, and I will do my best to make that happen.</p>

<p>I apologize for my bad English. I'm not an expert, and that's why I will do posts in English and in my native language that is Portuguese.</p>

<p>So, you're welcome, and let's get to work.</p>
]]></content>
        </entry>
    </feed>
